https://www.femaleforum.com/legal/

HomeForums
Our Members LoginRegister
All the legal mumbo-jumbo can be found below. If you have any additional questions, please get in touch.
Community GuidelinesTerms of UsePrivacy PolicyCommunity Guidelines
By accessing the site, you agree to be bound by the following community guidelines:
We do not allow:
The discussion of any illegal activity,
Sexually explicit or offensive language or content,
Inflammatory or defamatory comments, flaming or taunting,
Abuse or harassment of our staff or other members,
Abuse or disruption of our services,
The impersonation of Female Forum staff,
Copyrighted materials (articles, videos, audio, etc.) that you do not have permission to reproduce or distribute,
Duplicate content,
Advertising of third party services, products or websites that you are affiliated with or have an interest in unless authorized by us in advance and in writing.
You may link to one website in your forum signature, but it must not be accompanied with any promotional text. The link anchor text may only include the name of your site. Affiliate links are not permitted in signatures or posts under any circumstances.
You may only register one account. Those found to have registered more than one account risk an immediate ban. If you already have an account but cannot access it, or wish to change your username, please contact us.
If you ever need clarification on any part of our community guidelines or terms of use or have a question, suggestion, feedback or a problem with the site, please feel free to contact us.
Terms of Use
You must accept our terms below in order to use this website.
DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY
We do not warrant or assume any legal liability or responsibility whatsoever in respect of anything at all available in, on or from this website or linked to it. We do not endorse or recommend anything (including any products or services) which may be featured, used or referred to in or on this website. Any views, opinions or statements made or expressed in or on this website do not necessarily state or reflect ours (including those made by Community Reps and/or Forum Moderators) and they cannot be used for advertising or product endorsement purposes. Any links to other websites or information is simply for the convenience of users and we will not be responsible for the content or availability of these. We do not endorse or recommend anything (including any products or services) which are featured or used on those links to sites or information. In the same way neither do we endorse or recommend anything that comes in pop-up messages or advertisements while using this site.
You agree to any information you have entered on the site being stored in a database. While this information will not be disclosed to any third party without your consent we cannot be held responsible for any hacking attempt or system failure that may lead to the data being compromised or lost.
COPYRIGHT
The idea, format, layout and content of this website is subject to copyright and any duplication, copying or use in any way or all, some or any part of it will constitute a breach of copyright.
By submitting content to this website, you represent that you have a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive right (including any moral rights) and license to use, license, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, derive revenue or other remuneration from, communicate to the public, perform and display the content (in whole or in part) worldwide and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media, or technology now known or later developed, for the full term of any Rights that may exist in such content.
By submitting content to this website, you are granting Female Forum a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive right (including any moral rights) and license to use, license, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, derive revenue or other remuneration from, communicate to the public, perform and display the content (in whole or in part) worldwide and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media, or technology now known or later developed.
USERS MUST BE OVER 16 YEARS OLD AND COMPLY WITH ENGLISH LAW AND THIS NOTICE
This site may at times contain information, content, features, language, opinions, information, suggestions, products, services and references and other matters which are suitable only for persons over 16. Therefore this website, and any part of it, is only available to those who are over 16 years of age. This site operates in accordance with and complies with all elements of English law, including data protection. By continuing to the next page or visiting, using, viewing the whole or any part of it or having any involvement whatsoever with this website you are confirming that you are over 16 and will not misuse the website in any way and continue to use this site in accordance with and compliance with all elements of English law. If you are under 16 years of age or do not agree to be bound or abide by this notice then you are not authorized to or visit, use, view the whole or any part of it or have any involvement whatsoever with this website and must leave the website immediately. We reserve the right to take action against those who do not.
COMMUNITY GUIDELINES
By accessing the site, you agree to be bound by the following community guidelines:
By accessing the site, you agree to be bound by the following community guidelines:
We do not allow:
The discussion of any illegal activity,
Sexually explicit or offensive language or content,
Inflammatory or defamatory comments, flaming or taunting,
Abuse or harassment of our staff or other members,
Abuse or disruption of our services,
The impersonation of Female Forum staff,
Copyrighted materials (articles, videos, audio, etc.) that you do not have permission to reproduce or distribute,
Duplicate content,
Advertising of third party services, products or websites that you are affiliated with or have an interest in unless authorized by us in advance and in writing.
You may link to one website in your forum signature, but it must not be accompanied with any promotional text. The link anchor text may only include the name of your site. Affiliate links are not permitted in signatures or posts under any circumstances.
You may only register one account. Those found to have registered more than one account risk an immediate ban. If you already have an account but cannot access it, or wish to change your username, please contact us.
If you ever need clarification on any part of our community guidelines or terms of use or have a question, suggestion, feedback or a problem with the site, please feel free to contact us directly via the contact form to ensure that it receives the proper attention.
REMOVAL OF ACCESS & MODIFICATION OF INFORMATION
You accept that we reserve the right to refuse or delete your membership and access to any or all sections of this website at any time at our own discretion. We do not need to give you a reason should we decide to do this. You agree we have the right to remove or modify any information submitted to this website as we see fit.
We reserve the right to ban you if we feel you have broken any of our community guidelines; there may not be a warning prior to a ban. Depending upon the circumstances, we may pass your information onto your Internet Service Provider or the police. We also reserve the right to ban anyone we suspect of being under the age of 16 regardless of fact.
You accept that we reserve the right to change these terms at any time without notice and that it is your responsibility to ensure you are aware of any changes made to these terms.
ANY ACCESS OF THIS WEBSITE BY YOU SHALL BE DEEMED TO BE AN ACCEPTANCE OF THE ABOVE NOTICE AND CONFIRMATION OF THE ABOVE TERMS.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. Our privacy policy is set out below. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us.
The information Female Forum receives and how it is used
We have access to any and all information you submit to this website – for example, your email address if you provide it. We may use your email address to contact you with news about this site or products or services offered by third parties which we feel will be of interest to you. You can choose to opt-out of such communications by contacting us.
Information we hold about you will never be divulged to a third party and will always remain confidential to Female Forum and our staff unless you choose to publicly publish or share it with other users. Any personal information we collect from this website will be used in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws. We may reveal information about you in response to court orders or any legitimate request by authorities with which we must comply in order to satisfy legal obligations.
We will regularly log your IP address. This is your computer’s personal signature but is not linked to personally identifiable information. We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer and track the movements of users whilst on this site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may share any IP addresses we obtain from abusive users amongst Female Forum staff in order to help protect the security of our site. We may also use IP addresses to report such users to their Internet Service Provider or other higher authorities. We may also have to share information we hold about you in order to comply with any legal requirements.
We may collect data to enable us to recognize you and record how you use this website. This allows us to improve and personalize some of our services and can save you from re-entering information when you return to this website. Such data is collected by cookies during your time spent on this site. It is not possible to connect identities or specific persons with the content of a cookie.
A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. Almost all web browsers can be set to prevent cookies or ensure they are only created with your express permission. You will find more information on how to do this in the help section of your browser.
Google as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Female Forum cannot be held responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Your rights
We rarely hold or collect personally identifiable information on users however when we do, you have the right to see information held about you upon request. You can ask us to update or remove any personal information Female Forum holds about you at any time by contacting us. We will always work to help you as honestly and speedily as we can.
More information
If you have any further questions or want to know more, please contact us and we will reply as soon as possible.
More Articles
Love
These Are the Reasons Why You Are Attracted to Certain People
A Brief History of Dating and How Dating Has Changed Through the Ages
Do you see some weird obsession or is there something more to this story?
Forgot your password?
No account? Sign up
Lost Password
Please enter your username or email address. You will receive a link to create a new password via email.
Already have an account? Login instead
